Hi, in this lesson, I will help you to setup a I/O/SORM creator, and you can start using it.
So please open shows the link from the resources I shared for this lesson, and you will
see a croissor homepage.
You can click on download button, it will suggest automatically download it for your operation
system.
If you don't, you can click on all downloads and choose your operation system manually.
Now you can, of course, choose the previous version in case you need it, but I recommend
to use always a latest version.
Okay, let's click the download it, you see download, you'll start it, and now I view and
install it, okay, let's wait a few seconds, do I can run an application, okay, and now I can
start my application, okay, nice.
When you first time install a croissor, it suggests you to login to your account, I recommend
you to create an account, of course, or because I have an account, allow you to use
more AI features.
I already have an account that's why I click on login button, but if you don't have it,
you can click sign up.
You, of course, can do it later and skip the step, but I recommend you to create it right
now.
So, I will click on login, because I already have an account and I assign it in, it suggests
me to login it using my account and click yes login, and then open croissor again.
Also, if you use visuals to the code editor before and you have some settings like font
sizes, some, I know, some team configuration, some extensions, you can import all your settings
from visuals to the code, that's what I can, I will do.
You'll see a message that you'll be imported settings, extensions, and other profile preference,
and if you will have something in course already, you'll be replaced, but it's fine for
us.
You can also click on button import without an extensions if you don't like to use them.
I will click import.
You can choose one of them, could sort of suggest you, or you can click on export other
teams and choose any other team you like.
For example, I like to use button one dark team, and I will find it in click.
Also, could sort of show you some shortcuts, how you can call an ancient chat, cresor
app, and inline edit, but I also will explain this shortcuts later.
And if you use another code editor, you can also see how to do it.
Okay, and now we see some message about data sharing, as I ask, how improve cursor for
everyone, and say by default, cursor learns from code to help you get better experience during
control turn off anything in settings privacy, and data sharing is all the first day after
one day of use cursor stores and learn from your prompts, code base, edit history, and
other usage data to improve the product.
You can cause a read it more on a privacy settings and in security.
Okay, we can click on find cursor learning from my code, and we will turn it off in settings,
and we will do the during off within settings.
And now we can choose the preferred language we want to speak with cursor, I choose English.
And of course you can choose open from terminal, if you want, I want to use the settings,
but if you want to use the cursor command in terminal, you can click install and it will
install this command.
Okay, now it's run, let's open a cursor settings, cursor settings, and check the privacy.
So we see we have privacy mode, it's not set by default, any of the mode, I will choose privacy
mode, it's restarted, okay, it was set previously.
It's really weird that it won't be set by default, but we anyway set it twice.
Okay, I hope it will help you to stop your cursor application, and in the next version, I will
show you how we can weekly start using it, see you in the next version.